Hey everybody, welcome to this A1
English listening practice video. You
can use this video to train your
listening and comprehension as I speak.
You ready? So today I'm going to talk
about cooking. I do not know how to
cook. So I do not know a lot about this
topic. However, I like eating so I like
talking about food in general. I am
lucky because my wife cooks very well.
She has a natural talent for cooking.
So, she cooks well. That means that I
eat well. Let me tell you about some of
the things that my wife cooks. Since she
is Mexican, she likes cooking Mexican
food. Sometimes she makes tacos, which
are delicious. There are many types of
tacos, so my wife can cook different
tacos each time. I also cooked tacos in
the past, but I don't cook well, so my
tacos weren't very good. I cooked tacos
lenua, tongue tacos, but I didn't cook
them very well. My wife cooks much
better. The only thing that I cook well
is eggs. I love eggs and I eat them
almost every morning. I think eggs are
the best breakfast food. I usually eat
scrambled eggs, but I also eat other
types of eggs, too. My favorite type is
eggs benedict. M. This is my favorite
breakfast. Have you tried eggs benedict?
So, my wife also makes pasta. She makes
really good pasta. She doesn't buy the
pasta in the box that you buy from the
store. She makes the pasta by hand. She
makes the noodles and they taste so
good. When you make pasta by hand, it
tastes better. I love all types of
pasta, but my favorite is ravioli. For
me, ravioli is the perfect food.
Actually, I like all Italian food. When
we were in Italy, we ate some amazing
food. My wife also cooks a lot of meat.
We like eating different cuts of steak
every week. We try to buy cheap meat
because meat can be expensive. We don't
want to spend a lot of money, so we buy
cheap meat. My wife cooks the meat in a
pan, which is easy. Other people cook
their meat on a grill. We don't have a
grill, so we use a pan. I think that
meat tastes good if it's cooked on a pan
or on a grill. Meat is always good. I
hope my wife cooks meat tonight. She
also cooks really good breakfast. She
makes really good pancakes. I like to
eat pancakes with maple syrup and peanut
butter. I know that's a little strange,
but it's delicious. I love pancakes and
peanut butter. My wife also cooks
chilakilles, a common Mexican breakfast.
This is my favorite breakfast in the
world. I love chilakilles.
This dish has tortilla chips, salsa,
cheese, and cream. I like it with eggs
on top. It's so good. I don't know which
is better, breakfast or dinner. In my
family, we cook dinner 5 days a week.
The other days we go out to eat dinner
or we eat dinner with other people.
Sometimes we eat dinner with my parents
and other times we eat dinner with my
sister. Tonight we will eat dinner with
my parents and my mother will cook
dinner. When I was a kid, my mother
cooked dinner every weekday. Every
evening, we ate dinner at 6:30 p.m.
every day. Do you eat dinner at the same
time every day? In the US, it's common
for families to eat dinner together. We
sit together at the table. We eat and we
talk about our day. Dinner time is
important in the US. In other countries,
people eat dinner late, like at 8:00
p.m. or 900 p.m. But this is too late
for me. I don't want to eat dinner late.
I like eating dinner at 5, 6, or 700
p.m. This is a good time for dinner.
What do you like eating for dinner? I
like every type of food from every
country. I can eat anything and I love
trying new foods. Like I said, I don't
cook well, but I eat well. Maybe I will
learn to cook in the future, but I don't
know. I don't like cooking and I don't
have the natural talent to cook. I
prefer eating, not cooking. My wife
cooks very well, so I don't need to
learn. I'm thankful for that. Okay, we
are finished for today. Leave a comment
and tell me if you like cooking. I'll
see you next video.
[Music]
[Applause]